#### Resume

Ahmed Ali slim

HSE section head

Address: Ayat Giza

Phone: +01020099704/01110944268

Mail Me:

ahmedali**7532147**@gmail·com Date of Birth: 1/10/1996 Marital Status: married

Web Site:

https://ahmedali7532147-github-io/my-

website2/



#### **OBJECTIVE**

Safety and health engineer with 4 years of experience. worked in major construction companies such as Redcon construction, Arab developments. Cairo 3A food companies. In developing, implementing and establishing the Occupational Safety and Health and Risk Management and Evaluation Department. And seeking to join a work team in major leading companies Which seeks to achieve excellence in the field of occupational safety and health.



#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- ICDL, excellent
- fire marshal, excellent
- emergency drills, excellent
- work as iso 45001, excellent
- emergency respons plans, excellent
- environment awareness, excellent
- jon hazard analysis, excellent
- job safety analysis, excellent
- risk assessment, excellent
- TBT, excellent
- work permit, excellent
- cut welldingy, excellent
- construction safety, excellent
- continuous learning
- problem solving skills
- risk management
- risk assessment
- fire alarm system
- work law
- emergency planing
- safety awareness
- Coordination of the safety committee , very good
- Committee members
- emergency response plan
- accident reportation
- incident reportation
- accident investigation
- safety audit
- reports preparation
- safety training
- Microsoft outlook
- Microsoft office
- Microsoft excel
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- Microsoft word



#### **EXPERIENCE**

Head of the Occupational Safety and Health Department in the breeding sector and hatchery plant	
Safety and health supervisor, Redcon construction	2022/9-2023/9
safety officer, Arab developer	2021/8-2022/9



# **COURSES**

occupational safety and the healthy environment specialist NIOSH (advanced), Institute of Occupational Safety, Health and Work Environment Safety

occupational safety and the healthy environment specialist NIOSH (basic), Institute of 1 month Occupational Safety, Health and Work Environment Safety IOSH, Petro gold Safety committee members, Workers' Cultural Foundation 1 months **OSHA general and construction**, professional academy Hazard Idintification & Risk Assessment& control, Petro GoldFor Training & Consulting 5/10/2023 & Petroleum Services One week fire marshal, Civil protection in Giza 2024/1/13-2024/1/15 fire marshal, Civil Protection in Giza 1week first aid, Egyptian Crescent first aid,



## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor Agriculture engineering, Ain Shams

10/2016-6/2021



## **LANGUAGES**

- Arabic, native
- English, 50%
- German, start